* Menu

    Student Log-in
    
    * * *
    
    Teacher Log-in
    
    Sign up

    * * *

* * *

    Student Log-in
    
    * * *
    
    Teacher Log-in
    
    Sign up

    * * *
    
    Teacher Sign up

* Contact Us

On Sale
=======

15% off

The Billy & Gorro Winter Set: Scarf & Hat Combo ~$39.70~ $33.74 [Go to store](https://www.senorwooly.com/store/product/billy-y-gorro)

Are you ready?
==============

Not yet. Show me more! [Yes, let’s get started!](https://www.senorwooly.com/pricing)

Señor Wooly Privacy Policy
==========================

#### Our Privacy Principles

* We have been at the forefront of student privacy protections since the founding of our company in 2009. We have never collected any PII (Personally Identifiable Information) from children.
* We never sell or share any user’s information with third parties.
* We never track users’ online behavior outside of Señor Wooly.
* We do not market and/or intentionally sell any products of any kind to children.
* We comply with all state and federal privacy guidelines and laws for minors (COPPA and FERPA, for example).

#### Overview

Wooly Learning, Inc. (“Señor Wooly”, “Wooly Learning”, “our”, “us”, or “we”) is committed to keeping all users’ personal information safe and private. The purpose of this privacy policy is to provide users of our website with information regarding the type of personal information we collect, and how it is used. For detailed information about privacy provisions applicable to children/minors, please see the section beginning with **Children's Privacy**.

#### Your consent

By using our website, you consent to our privacy policy and our terms and conditions. This policy was last modified on April 20, 2022 and governs the use of our website and information associated with the purchase of products through our website. We encourage you to refer to this policy periodically so that you understand our current privacy policies.

#### What information do we collect?

* We collect information from you when you register on the website, place an order, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another website feature.
* When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, name of school where you work, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our website anonymously. 
* Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use cookies?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, respond to a survey or marketing communication, browse the website, or use certain other website features in the following ways:

* Providing the service.
* To personalize your website experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
* To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
* To quickly process your transactions.
* To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other website feature.
* For marketing and promotional purposes related to Wooly Learning, Inc. We never share your information with outside parties.
* If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please send us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.senorwooly.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with the subject line “Unsubscribe”. You can also click on the link "Unsubscribe" which is located in all email newsletters.

#### How do we protect visitor information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All information you supply, including but not limited to sensitive information like login credentials and credit information, is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We do not store any credit card information.

In addition, we ensure that all data transactions and transfers with our customers are encrypted.

We cannot, however, ensure or guarantee the security of any or all of the information you transmit to Wooly Learning, Inc. For example, no Internet service or email message is guaranteed to be fully secure. In particular, emails sent to or from Wooly Learning, Inc. may not be secure. Please take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email or for support help. Once we receive your transmission of information, Wooly Learning, Inc. makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems.

In the event that information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and will then notify you of the incident in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the website's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use two types of cookies—session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies exist only for the duration of time you have your internet browser open when you visit our site and are used for functions such as remembering and processing items in your shopping cart. Persistent cookies do not disappear when you exit your browser, but instead persist each time you visit our website. These cookies are used to help us better understand your preferences based on previous or current website activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about website traffic and website interaction so that we can offer better website experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our website visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Mozilla Firefox or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your website experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

#### Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. The term "outside parties" does not include Wooly Learning, Inc. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

#### How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?

To modify your e-mail subscriptions or other information that you have provided to us, please click “Unsubscribe” within the e-mail newswletter. You can also email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.senorwooly.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to request removal.

To delete all of your online account information from our database, please send us a request via e-mail at [\[email protected\]](https://www.senorwooly.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Please note that we may continue to maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for internal record keeping purposes.

#### Third party links

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our website. These linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites. These linked websites are only for your convenience and therefore you access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, Wooly Learning, Inc. seeks to protect the integrity of our website and welcomes any feedback about these linked websites (including if a specific link does not work).

#### Single-Sign-On (SSO) authentication services

If you decide to register for an account (or create a secondary connection in order to access your account) through an authentication service (such as Google Accounts, ClassLink, or Clever as a Single-Sign-On, also known as a SSO) (“Authentication Service”), we may collect information from these third-party services, consistent with the privacy settings in your account with the relevant Authentication Service.

#### Changes to our policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this “Señor Wooly Privacy Policy” page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

#### California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code §§ 1798.83-.84 provide users that are California residents with a right to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we may share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As noted above, we do not currently provide personally identifiable information to third parties for direct marketing purposes.

#### Questions and feedback

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy or this policy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue by contacting us via phone at (224) 935-3088 or by mail at Wooly Learning, Inc., P.O. Box 903, Skokie, IL 60076.

#### Online Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please visit our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.senorwooly.com/terms/) section, which establishes use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

### Children’s Privacy

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and other laws have been established to protect the privacy of minors. At Wooly Learning, Inc., we take the privacy rights of our users, especially children, very seriously, and abide by all federal and state laws and guidelines regarding youth privacy. The following outlines our general children’s privacy guidelines:

Wooly Learning, Inc. exists to serve educators, parents and students and strives to provide a safe, positive experience for children. To ensure this, we adhere to the following policies:

* We do not knowingly collect online contact information directly from children ages 13 and younger.
* We do not distribute any personally identifiable information about children to third parties.
* We do not allow students to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information.
* We do not use the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to entice children to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.

Wooly Learning, Inc. provides an online service marketed towards educators. The services we provide to students/minors are solely for the use and benefit of their school, and for no other commercial purpose. To that end, COPPA allows the school of the student/minor to act as the parent’s agent, and can consent to the collection of child’s information on the parent’s behalf. 

##### What information do you collect from students/minors?

We do not collect any personal information from students with the exception of first name, the first letter of the last name, and the school they attend.  Teachers have the option of changing a setting in order to allow for the input of students’ last names.  Teachers will only enable this option if the school district has given consent to do so. If the teacher, school, or school district wishes to delete these last names, they can do so by changing the setting back to last name initial only, after which all full last names will be permanently deleted from the server.  

This information is gathered from the students directly, and not through the use of cookies. This information will only be used by their teacher in order to distinguish them from their classmates. **This information will never be disclosed to third parties for any reason.**

##### How do we use this personal information?

Wooly Learning, Inc. never directly uses the personal information provided by children except to aid in troubleshooting and the functioning of the application. Only teachers or their agents use the information, to distinguish between students in their class.

##### Does Wooly Learning, Inc. use or share the information for commercial purposes not related to the provision of the online services requested by the school? For instance, does Wooly Learning, Inc. use the students’ personal information in connection with online behavioral advertising, or building use profiles for commercial purposes not related to the provision of the online service?

No.

##### Does Wooly Learning, Inc. enable the school to review and have deleted the personal information collected from their students?

Yes, at any time. Requests should be sent to [\[email protected\]](https://www.senorwooly.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

##### What measures does Wooly Learning, Inc. take to protect the security, confidentiality, and integrity of the personal information that it collects?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

##### Does Wooly Learning, Inc. have a breach policy?

Yes. In the event that information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and will then notify you of the incident in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

##### Child Usage of Single-Sign-On (SSO) authentication services

If a child registers an account through an authentication service (such as Google Accounts, ClassLink, or Clever as a Single-Sign-On, also known as a SSO), we may collect information from these third-party services, consistent with the privacy settings in the teacher’s umbrella account with the relevant Authentication Service. The decision to use an authentication service is made by the teacher, not the child. The teacher will select the authentication method at the class level, which is then adopted by all children within that class as they register their accounts.

##### What are Wooly Learning, Inc.’s data retention and deletion policies for children’s personal information?

All information provided by children is kept under the umbrella account of their teacher. The teacher can, at any time, permenently delete the student from their umbrella account, which will permanently erase all personal information from Wooly Learning, Inc. servers. That said, Wooly Learning, Inc. can also delete students’ personal information. This can be requested by sending a notice of the request to Wooly Learning, Inc. at [\[email protected\]](https://www.senorwooly.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Such request must include the name, teacher’s name, and school of the minor making the request and the posted information, material and content on the website they are requesting to have removed. Upon receipt of such a request, Wooly Learning, Inc. will remove material, information, and content posted on the website, including answers, results, scores, and other information provided as part of the use of programs, applications, practice activities, quizzes, or tests on the website.

##### Parental Rights

Wooly Learning, Inc. will never require a child to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity. At any time, parents can review their child’s personal information, direct us to delete it, and refuse to allow any further collection of use of the child’s information.  

##### On-Line Eraser for Minors In California

California law provides for the ability of minors that are registered users of the website to request and obtain removal of material, information, and content posted on the website. Registered users 17 years of age or younger who are California residents, may request Wooly Learning, Inc. to remove their own posted content on the website by sending a notice of the request to Wooly Learning, Inc. at [\[email protected\]](https://www.senorwooly.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Such request must include the name, teacher’s name, and school of the minor making the request and the posted information, material and content on the website they are requesting to have removed. Upon receipt of such a request, Wooly Learning, Inc. will remove material, information, and content posted on the website, including answers, results, scores, and other information provided as part of the use of programs, applications, practice activities, quizzes, or tests on the website. Please note that in complying with such a request, the posted information, material, and content will no longer be visible to other users of the website or public, including teachers, schools, and school officials who have set up the programs, applications, practice activities, quizzes, or tests as part of a school program or class activity. The material, information, and content will not be deleted from the Wooly Learning, Inc. server; it will just no longer be visible or accessible by other users or the general public. There are exceptions to complying to the request where the posted information, material, and content will not be removed from visibility to or access by other users, such as where federal or state law requires Wooly Learning, Inc. or its third parties to maintain the information, material, and content, the information, material, and content is stored on or posted to the Wooly Learning, Inc. website by a third party, the information, material, and content is provided and maintained anonymously, the minor fails to follow the instructions regarding removal, or the minor has received compensation or other consideration for providing the information, material, and content.

* Contact Us
* Changelog

### Want all the latest Señor Wooly updates?

Sign up for our newsletter:

  Sign up

© 2023 Wooly Learning, Inc.

What would you like to learn more about?
========================================

Talk to us!
===========

Please enter your comments, concerns, or compliments, and someone from the **Wooly Team** will get back to you as soon as possible!

 Your Name

 Your Email Address

 Your subject

Support Sales General

Send Message This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms) apply.

 close

Examples: Billy present tense tener tutorial scarf graphic novel horror poster body parts

### Stories based on ""

No results found...

Tip: try one of the above examples

### Other

No results found...

Tip: try one of the above examples

×

#### Log in / Sign up

##### Log In

 [ Sign in with Google](https://www.senorwooly.com/api/v2/auth/student/google/start/?redirect=true) Classic log in  

##### Sign Up

To create a new account, click the button below. You'll need the class code given to you by your teacher.

Sign Up

##### Log In

Find Your School

To log back in, start by finding your school. Don't see it? Tell your teacher to contact us, and we'll get it fixed right away.

\-- Select Your Country -- United States Afghanistan Albania Algeria American Samoa Andorra Angola Anguilla Antarctica Antigua and Barbuda Argentina Armenia Aruba Australia Austria Azerbaijan Bahamas Bahrain Bangladesh Barbados Belarus Belgium Belize Benin Bermuda Bhutan Bolivia Bosnia and Herzegovina Botswana Bouvet Island Brazil British Indian Ocean Territory British Virgin Islands Brunei Bulgaria Burkina Faso Burundi Cambodia Cameroon Canada Cape Verde Cayman Islands Central African Republic Chad Chile China Christmas Island Cocos \[Keeling\] Islands Colombia Comoros Congo \[DRC\] Congo \[Republic\] Cook Islands Costa Rica Côte d'Ivoire Croatia Cuba Curaçao Cyprus Czech Republic Denmark Djibouti Dominica Dominican Republic Ecuador Egypt El Salvador Equatorial Guinea Eritrea Estonia Ethiopia Falkland Islands \[Islas Malvinas\] Faroe Islands Fiji Finland France French Guiana French Polynesia French Southern Territories Gabon Gambia Gaza Strip Georgia Germany Ghana Gibraltar Greece Greenland Grenada Guadeloupe Guam Guatemala Guernsey Guinea Guinea-Bissau Guyana Haiti Heard Island and McDonald Islands Honduras Hong Kong Hungary Iceland India Indonesia Iran Iraq Ireland Isle of Man Israel Italy Jamaica Japan Jersey Jordan Kazakhstan Kenya Kiribati Kosovo Kuwait Kyrgyzstan Laos Latvia Lebanon Lesotho Liberia Libya Liechtenstein Lithuania Luxembourg Macau Macedonia \[FYROM\] Madagascar Malawi Malaysia Maldives Mali Malta Marshall Islands Martinique Mauritania Mauritius Mayotte Mexico Micronesia Moldova Monaco Mongolia Montenegro Montserrat Morocco Mozambique Myanmar \[Burma\] Namibia Nauru Nepal Netherlands New Caledonia New Zealand Nicaragua Niger Nigeria Niue Norfolk Island Northern Mariana Islands North Korea Norway Oman Pakistan Palau Palestinian Territories Panama Papua New Guinea Paraguay Peru Philippines Pitcairn Islands Poland Portugal Puerto Rico Qatar Réunion Romania Russia Rwanda Saint Eustatius and Saba Saint Helena Saint Kitts and Nevis Saint Lucia Saint Pierre and Miquelon Saint Vincent and the Grenadines Samoa San Marino São Tomé and Príncipe Saudi Arabia Senegal Serbia Seychelles Sierra Leone Singapore Sint Maarten Slovakia Slovenia Solomon Islands Somalia South Africa South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands South Korea Spain Sri Lanka Sudan Suriname Svalbard and Jan Mayen Swaziland Sweden Switzerland Syria Taiwan Tajikistan Tanzania Thailand Timor-Leste Togo Tokelau Tonga Trinidad and Tobago Tunisia Turkey Turkmenistan Turks and Caicos Islands Tuvalu Uganda Ukraine United Arab Emirates United Kingdom Uruguay U.S. Minor Outlying Islands U.S. Virgin Islands Uzbekistan Vanuatu Vatican City Venezuela Vietnam Wallis and Futuna Western Sahara Yemen Zambia Zimbabwe

Select Your Teacher \-- Select Your Teacher -- Don't see your teacher? Select a different school.

Select Your Class \-- Select Your Class --

 Show archived classes

Select Your Name \-- Select Your Name --

Forgot your password?

Back Next Clear Login  
  
Step 1 / 5

##### Sign Up

To create a new account, click the button below.

You'll need the class code given to you by your teacher.

Sign Up

##### Log In with Google

##### Or log in with email and password

Email 

Password 

Forgot your password?

Invalid username or password.

##### Sign Up

Ready to choose your plan and get started?
